(Bernadette:)I made him tell us.
"Us"? Who else knows?
(Bernadette:)- I know.
- Me too.
(Leonard:)Same here.
(Raj:)Shame on all of you.
(Leonard:)You know too.
Couldn't leave him with one friend,
could you?
(Howard:)So everybody knows what's in that letter
except for me?
(Sheldon:)Yes, it's six against one.
Stand down, sir.
(Howard:)How could you do this?
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
- Lf you want, we could tell you.
- I don't want to know.
(Leonard:)I mean...
(Howard:)I do, but...
I gotta go.
Used me as a human shield?
(Sheldon:)I panicked.
(Sheldon:)He looked taller than usual.
(Bernadette(off):)Howard?
(Howard:)In here.
(Sheldon:)Sorry.
I should've left it alone.
It's okay. I'm sorry I ran off like that.